onehopewine.com 2017-02-11

# Privacy | ONEHOPE Wine

### Our Commitment to Privacy

 **ONE** HOPE Wine is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy as a visitor to our website at http://www.onehopewine.com. We take the issue of privacy very seriously and value the trust you place in us each time you use our services and access this website. This Privacy Statement describes the practices and policies we have put into place to safeguard your personal information that may be gathered and used as you visit our website.

The policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, we encourage you to contact us using any of the methods outlined at the end of our Privacy Statement.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, you are not authorized to use this site.

### Who Is Collecting the Information?

 **ONE** HOPE Wine is collecting information on this Web site as outlined in this privacy statement.

### What Information Do We Collect?

 _Automatic Collection of Information:_

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website or download information, our system will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our web site and tell us the number of visitors to our site each day.

Our Web server automatically collects and records the following information:

  * The visitor’s domain name and e-mail address, when possible.
  * The visitor’s domain name, but not the e-mail address.
  * The visitor’s IP address.
  * Aggregate information on what pages are accessed.
  * The name and release number of web browser software used.
  * The operating system used.
  * Date and time you access our site.
  * The address of the Web site that linked to us (referrer URL).

 _Permission-based Collection of Information:_

At different places on our site depending upon the feature you use, you may be asked to volunteer personal information such as your name, email, mailing address, and telephone number.

### How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

The information we gather automatically and with your permission during your visit to our Web site is used in the following ways:

  * Monitor, review, measure, and analyze Web site utilization
  * Modify and enhance the Web site
  * Improve the content and design of our Web site
  * Determine the need for new programs and services
  * Respond to your requests
  * Customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor
  * Monitor and improve our customer service efforts
  * Study general usage habits and demographic information for our own marketing research purposes
  * Distribute news and other information requested by Web visitors
  * Notify visitors about updates to our Web site
  * Determine the effectiveness of special promotion and marketing programs
  * Contact consumers for marketing purposes

Notwithstanding anything in this agreement to the contrary, you understand and agree that **ONE** HOPE Wine may access, preserve and disclose any submitted information or otherwise use information we have received about you: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or when otherwise required by law, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend any legal claims; (2) to protect the rights and property of **ONE** HOPE Wine or other entity; (3) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding unauthorized distribution of a third party’s intellectual property, illegal activities, fraud or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (4) to any of our related companies or companies under common control with **ONE** HOPE Wine; and (5) if **ONE** HOPE Wine is acquired by or merged with another entity. We may also use information we have received about you to resolve disputes or to investigate problems. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our website, products and services. Specifically, we may use information such as your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage the **ONE** HOPE Wine website or to enhance the **ONE** HOPE Wine website based on the usage pattern data we receive.

### With Whom Will the Information Be Shared?

The personally identifiable information gathered during your visit to this Web site is not shared with any organization for any purpose.

### Additional Use of Personal Information

 _Requesting No E-mail Communication_

You may receive e-mail messages from us about special promotions, upcoming events and other relevant information that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such email messages, please let us know by the following means:

  * Sending us e-mail to that effect at: privacy@onehopewine.com
  * Calling us by telephone at: (866) 983-2266
  * Writing to us at the contact address: P.O. Box 1117, Newport Beach, CA 92659-1117
  * Visiting the following URL: www.onehopewine.com/customer/account

 _Requesting No Postal Mailings_

You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by the following means:

  * Sending us e-mail to that effect at: privacy@onehopewine.com
  * Calling us by telephone at: (866) 983-2266
  * Writing to us at the contact address: P.O. Box 1117, Newport Beach, CA 92659-1117

### Our Use of Cookies

Many Web sites now use “cookies” to provide useful features to their visitors by providing customizable and personalized services.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. For example, a Web site may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you, your preferences, or the pages you last visited.

Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies, or to ask you if you would like to accept or decline a cookie from a particular site before it is set. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the Help section of the toolbar. You should know, however, that if you reject a cookie, certain functions and conveniences of a site may not work properly.

We use cookies on our Web site for the following purposes:

  * Store and sometimes track visitor preferences
  * Store personal identifying information
  * Record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart.
  * Record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit
  * Alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site
  * To record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site
  * Customize web page content on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends

### Registration for Access

Some Web sites require you to provide some personal information through a registration process in order to take advantage of certain Web site features and to access content areas. For example, a registration form might request your name, telephone number and e-mail address.

Access to some of the features on this Web site requires registration, and the disclosure of some personal information, which may include:

  * Billing and shipping information

### Our Children’s Privacy Policy

Our site does not feature information and services of interest to children or anyone under the age of 21.

### Interactive Services and Tools

Interactive services tools and other technology-based features provide Web site users with a richer and more valuable experience. The tools can provide you with information that is customized according to your personal needs.

This site does not use interactive tools that ask you for identifying personal information.

### Security of Communications

We recognize that many people are concerned about the privacy and protection of information as it is transmitted over the Internet. You should keep in mind that the possibility exists for unauthorized individuals to intercept any email message you send over the Internet. In some cases, information can be encrypted (scrambled or encoded) to make it very difficult to read if it is intercepted during communication. Certain technology and practices allow Web sites to provide an increased level of security for your personal information when appropriate.

We use the following practices on our Web site to enhance the level of security for communication and the transmission of personal information:

  * We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site
  * We have taken reasonable steps to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of personally identifiable information that you may provide.
  * We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site

### E-Commerce and Online Shopping

Purchasing items over the Internet usually requires you to provide your personal identifying information and credit card information on a Web site. Many people have become accustomed to on-line commerce as a time-saving and useful convenience. There are a number of practices that can make providing your sensitive credit card information more secure and therefore make you feel more comfortable about doing so.

We do process credit card payments for merchandise, or services on our Web site. We have the following e-commerce practices:

  * When processing your credit card payment, we will ask for the card type, number, expiration date, and your card’s billing address.
  * We will transmit credit card numbers in an encrypted format using industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
  * We will keep this information in the strictest confidence and will make every effort to maintain the privacy and security of the information at all times.

### Advertising Servers

On-line advertising, such as banner ads, has become commonplace on many Web sites. Certain Web sites have developed relationships with third-party advertising servers to display these advertisements on their sites. By clicking on one of these banner ads, you will be taken to another site with different privacy policies. These third party ad servers may also use cookies to collect non-personal information on your preferences and interests via the advertisement you decide to view.

At this time, we do not partner with or have special relationships with any advertising server companies.

### Links to Other Sites

Web sites often provide a number of links that offer direct access to other useful or interesting web sites holding potential value to site visitors. Inclusion of the other sites by links does not imply any endorsement of the material or information on the other sites. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of each linked site before sharing personal information.

This site includes links to non-affiliated external Web sites. We have the following practices:

  * We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each linked site, as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we have the following practices:

  * We will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

 _  
Preference for Future Use of Information_

You may prevent your information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by:

  * Sending us e-mail to that effect at: info@onehopewine.com
  * Calling us by telephone at: (866) 983-2266
  * Writing to us at the contact address

### Web Site Contact Information

If you have questions about our privacy policy, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us.

 **ONEHOPE Wine**  
P.O. Box 1117  
Newport Beach, CA 92659-1117

E-mail: info@onehopewine.com  
Telephone: (866) 983-2266

### Modification and Effective Date

This privacy statement was last modified on March 26, 2015.
